Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Jones, James Earl
    - Blood Knot
      - Film
        - Correspondence, 1968-1971, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1964-1971, undated
        - Notes
          - 1968-1969
          - 1970-1971, undated, (3 folders) (Box 336)
        - Script, undated
      - Off-Broadway production, 1964
      - Other productions, 1964-1967, undated
    - Blood Tide (alternate title Red Tide )
      - Contracts, 1980-1981
      - Correspondence, 1980-1986
      - Miscellany, 1980-1981, undated
      - Notes, 1980-1981, undated
      - Script, undated
    - The Blue Abyss, 1964, undated
    - Boesman and Lena
      - Film, 1970-1971, undated
      - Miscellany, 1971-1976, undated
      - Off-Broadway production
        - Contracts, 1969-1970
        - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 337)
        - Financial records
          - Profit participation, 1970-1971
          - Salary, 1970
        - Miscellany, 1970, undated
        - Notes, 1970, undated
        - Press clippings, 1970
    - Bohikee Creek, 1966, 1978-1979, undated
    - “Boxing's Best: Jack Johnson,” 1982
    - The Boys Next Door, 1987
    - Bravo Television Network, 1983-1984
    - Brotherhood of the North, 1974-1977, undated, (3 folders)
    - The Brothers, 1970-1971
    - The Bushido Blade, 1978, undated
    - Caedmon Records sound recordings
      - Emperor Jones See Container 344, Emperor Jones
      - Financial records, 1971-1987, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1973-1978, undated
      - Native Son, 1973 (Box 338)
      - Poems of Black Africa, 1970
      - To Be Young, Gifted, and Black, 1970-1971, 1990, undated
      - Uncle Remus and Up from Slavery, 1975-1980
    - Calvin Luther, 1982
    - “Camera Three,” 1961, 1976-1977
    - “A Carol for Another Christmas,” 1964
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 1986-1988, 1994, undated, (3 folders)
    - Catch My Soul, 1967-1969
    - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, New York, N.Y., documentary, 1993-1994
    - “The Catholic Hour,” 1961
    - Catto Street, 1971
    - The Cay
      - Contracts, 1974
      - Correspondence, 1971-1979, 1994, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1974, undated
      - Notes, 1971-1974, undated, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1974 (Box 339)
      - Script, 1974
    - “CBS Library Afterschool Special,” “Beauty and the Beast,” 1980-1981
    - Chaka, 1970-1972, undated, (2 folders)
    - The Chancellor Manuscript, 1980-1981
    - “Channel 2 The People,” 1975-1978
    - “Channing,” 1964, undated
    - Chappie (a prospective film on the life of Gen. Daniel James), 1978-1987, undated, (2 folders)
    - “Chappie and Me,” 1980-1981
    - Charlottesville, Albemarle County, Va., bicentennial film, 1976
    - The Cherry Orchard
      - New York Shakespeare Festival, New York, N.Y.
        - Contracts, 1972-1973
        - Financial records, 1972-1973
        - Miscellany, 1972-1973, undated
        - Notes, 1972, undated
        - Press clippings, 1972-1973, undated
    - Christophe, 1969-1972, 1978-1980, undated, (2 folders) (Box 340)
    - Chrysalis Records, 1976, undated
    - “Circus of the Stars,” 1977
    - “City Hall,” 1987, undated
    - “City Limits”
      - Miscellany, 1983-1984, undated
      - Script, undated
    - “The Civil War,” 1987
    - Clandestine on the Morning Line, 1961-1962
    - Claudine See also Container 383, Third World Cinema
      - Contracts, 1973-1974
      - Correspondence, 1973-1979, (2 folders)
      - Financial records, 1974-1988, (4 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1973-1974, undated
      - Notes, 1973-1975, undated (Box 341)
      - Press clippings, 1973-1975, undated
      - Sequel or television series, 1974, undated
    - Coma, 1977
    - The Comedians
      - Correspondence, 1966-1967, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1966-1967, undated
    - Coming to America, 1987-1989, undated
    - “Community Crackdown,” 1991, undated
    - Conan the Barbarian
      - Contracts, 1980-1981, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982, undated
      - Financial records, 1980-1981
      - Notes, 1980-1983, undated, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1980-1982
    - Convicts, 1979-1990, undated (Box 342)
    - Coriolanus, 1978
    - “The Cosby Show,” 1986-1988, undated
    - Counter-Evans Surinam expedition documentary, 1974-1981, undated
    - The Coup, 1978-1979
    - The Cowboys, 1970-1972, undated
    - The Creation, 1980-1987
    - “The Cultural History of Negro Baseball,” 1980
    - “Dance in America,” “Divine Drumbeats: Katherine Dunham and Her People,” 1980
    - The Day It All Went to Hell
      - Miscellany, 1976-1981
      - Script, undated
    - Day of the Picnic, 1983-1984, undated
    - “A Day without Sunshine,” 1975-1976, undated
    - Deadly Hero
      - Contracts, 1975
      - Correspondence, 1975-1978
      - Miscellany, 1975-1976, undated
      - Notes, 1975-1976, undated
    - The Deep, 1976
    - “The Defenders,” 1962-1965
    - Defiant Island, 1970, undated (Box 343)
    - “Desiderata” recording, 1990, undated
    - “Diamonds in the Dust: Baseball and the American Dream,” 1987
    - Dick Gregory's Run Against Hunger, 1976-1977
    - Don't Go Away Mad
      - Correspondence, 1984-1988, undated
      - Miscellany, 1988, undated
      - Notes, 1984-1988, undated, (3 folders)
    - “Dr. Kildare,” 1964-1966
    - Dr. Strangelove
      - Correspondence, 1963
      - Miscellany, 1963-1969, undated
    - The Dream Awake filmstrip series, 1969-1970
    - Driving Miss Daisy, 1987-1988
    - “Eagle Flight,” 1987-1988, undated
    - “Earth Lab,” 1972
    - “Earth Works,” 1992-1993
    - “East Side/West Side,” 1963-1964, 1979, undated
    - Education Audio Visual sound filmstrip on Edgar Allan Poe, 1978, 1984 (Box 344)
    - The Egghead, 1957
    - Emperor Jones
      - Boston Arts Festival, Boston, Mass., 1964, undated
      - Caedmon Records, 1969-1972, undated, (4 folders)
      - Chicago Radio Theatre, Chicago, Ill., 1976-1981, undated
      - European tour, 1966-1968, 1977, undated, (3 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1921
      - Potential productions, 1969-1975
      - Studio Museum in Harlem, New York, N.Y., 1986-1987
    - “The End of the Dialogue,” 1973-1974
    - The End of the Road
      - Miscellany, 1968-1970, undated See also Oversize
      - Script, 1968
    - “Essence, The Television Program,” 1985-1987, undated
    - The Evangelist, 1980-1981
    - Exorcist II: The Heretic, 1976-1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 345)
    - “Fairie Tale Theatre,” “Aladdin and His Wonderful Lamp,” 1984-1986
    - Fences
      - Broadway production
        - Contracts, 1986-1987, (3 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1986-1993, undated, (3 folders)
        - Financial records
          - Miscellany, 1986-1987
          - Profit participation, 1987-1988, (11 folders) (Box 346)
          - Salary, 1987-1988, (4 folders) (Box 347)
        - Miscellany, 1986-1987, undated
        - Notes, 1985-1987, undated, (6 folders)
        - Playbills, 1987
        - Press clippings
          - 1986
          - 1987-1988, undated, (5 folders) (Box 348)
      - Film
        - Correspondence, 1986-1990
        - Notes, 1987-1989, undated
        - Press clippings, 1987-1991
        - Script, 1989
      - Goodman Theatre, Chicago, Ill.
        - Correspondence, 1985-1986
        - Financial records, 1986
        - Miscellany, 1985-1986, undated
        - Press clippings, 1985-1986
      - James A. Doolittle Theatre, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 349)
        - Contracts, 1988, undated
        - Correspondence, 1988-1990
        - Financial records
          - Profit participation, 1988, (2 folders)
          - Salary, 1988
        - Miscellany, 1988
        - Notes, 1988, undated, (2 folders)
        - Press clippings, 1988-1989
      - Miscellany, 1994, undated
      - Prospective productions
        - London, England, 1987-1988, undated
        - Washington, D.C., 1988, undated
      - Yale Repertory Theatre, New Haven, Conn.
        - Financial records, 1985
        - Miscellany, 1984-1988, undated
        - Printed matter, 1983-1985
        - Script, undated (Box 350)
    - Field of Dreams, 1988-1996, undated
    - First Liberty, 1988
    - Flight of Dragons, 1980, undated
    - Flight to Canada, 1977-1979, 1986, undated, (3 folders)
    - “Focus on Black,” 1969
    - Ford's Theatre Sound and Light Show, Washington, D.C., 1969-1970, undated
    - Forty Lashes Less One, 1971
    - The Four Seasons, 1981
    - Frederick Douglass, 1991
    - Free to Be...a Family, 1988, undated
    - “Freedom to Speak,” 1982-1983
    - Freeman, 1973-1974
    - “Fuzz Brothers,” 1972
    - Gabriel's Fire, 1989-1991, undated (Box 351)
    - Gardens of Stone
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1986-1987, undated
      - Notes, 1986-1987, undated
      - Press clippings, 1987
    - Gene Frankel Workshop videocassette series, 1977-1978
    - “Genius on the Black Side,” 1974-1979, undated, (2 folders)
    - The Golden Moment, 1980, undated
    - Grand Central Terminal documentary, 1982, undated
    - Great American Documents sound recording, 1975-1980
    - “Great Bears of Alaska,” 1992-1993
    - “Great Moments in Black History,” 1980
    - The Great White Hope (Box 352)
      - Arena Stage, Washington, D.C.
        - Correspondence, 1967-1968
        - Miscellany, 1967, undated
        - Playbills, 1967-1968
        - Press clippings, 1967-1968, undated
      - Broadway production
        - Article by James Earl Jones, 1968-1969
        - Contracts, 1968-1969
        - Correspondence, 1968-1972, undated
        - Financial records, 1968-1969, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1968
        - Press clippings, 1968-1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Promotional appearances, 1968-1969, (3 folders)
      - Film
        - Contracts, 1968-1970 See also Container 383, Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corp., (2 folders)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1971, (3 folders) (Box 353)
        - Financial records, 1968-1971
        - Miscellany, 1968-1970
        - Notes, 1968-1975, undated, (2 folders)
        - Press clippings, 1968-1971, undated, (2 folders)
      - London, England, production, 1969-1970, undated
      - Photographs, undated, (2 folders)
      - Sound recording, 1968-1970, undated
    - The Greatest, 1976-1977, undated
    - The Greatest Thing That Almost Happened, 1977, undated
    - Grendel (Box 354)
      - Miscellany, 1971-1980
      - Scripts, 1974, (2 folders)
    - “Guiding Light,” 1966-1967
    - “Guyana Tragedy: The Story of Jim Jones,” 1979-1985, undated, (3 folders)
    - Hamlet
      - Film, 1980
      - New York Shakespeare Festival, New York, N.Y., 1972
    - A Hand Is on the Gate, 1966
    - Happy Ending and Day of Absence, 1966
    - “Happy Endings,” 1974-1975, (2 folders)
    - “A Hard Road to Glory,” 1984-1986, undated
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., Learning from Performers program, 1976-1977
    - Hedda Gabler, 1981
    - “Hepatitis–The Invisible Epidemic,” 1991 (Box 355)
    - Her First American, 1986-1987, undated
    - “Hill Street Blues,” 1975-1984
    - Honky Tonk Nights
      - Miscellany, 1983, undated
      - Script, 1983
    - Hot Springs Documentary Film Festival, Hot Springs, Ark., 1993
    - Howard Thurman Educational Trust program, 1986
    - Howard University, Washington, D.C., slide show narration, 1979-1980, undated
    - Huck and Jim, 1981
    - Hunt for Red October, 1989-1990
    - Hunting of the Snark, 1982
    - “Hypertension: No. 1 Killer in Black America,” 1987-1988, undated, (3 folders)
    - The Iceman Cometh, 1973-1974, undated
    - If the World Goes Away, Where Will the Children Play? 1983
    - “I'm a People,” 1971, undated
    - In the Mood, 1982, undated
    - Infidel Caesar, 1962
    - “Insects: The Little Things That Run the World,” Smithsonian Video Collection, 1988-1989
    - Inside the NFL (Where Are They Now?) 1987 (Box 356)
    - International Business Machines employee events, 1990-1992, undated
    - International Poetry Forum, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1982, 1992, undated
    - Ira Aldridge
      - Correspondence, 1968-1980, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1975-1977, undated
      - Notes, 1969-1980, undated
      - Script, 1975, undated
    - Isom Dart and the Tip Galt Gang, 1980-1981, (3 folders)
    - Ivory Hunters, 1990, undated (Box 357)
    - “Ivory Wars,” 1989-1992, undated
    - Jackie Robinson Foundation video narration, 1991
    - James Earl Jones: Voices and Silences
      - Contracts, 1987-1989
      - Correspondence, 1987-1993, (4 folders)
      - Interview transcripts, 1987, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1987, 1993
      - Notes, 1987-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 358)
      - Reviews, 1993
    - Jazz Requiem for Martin Luther King, Jr., 1969, undated
    - Jesus of Nazareth
      - Correspondence, 1975-1977
      - Miscellany, 1975-1977
      - Notes, 1975-1979, undated
      - Scripts, parts 2-6, 1975, (5 folders)
    - John Henry
      - Film, 1977, undated
      - Sound recording, 1974-1975, undated
    - Jose Torres, 1965
    - King, 1975-1977, undated
    - King David narration, 1982
    - King Lear
      - King Lear-in-Performance Conference, University of Notre Dame, Notre Dame, Ind., 1983
      - New York Shakespeare Festival, New York, N.Y., 1973-1975, undated
    - King Oedipus, 1976-1977, undated See also Oversize (Box 359)
    - King of Paris, 1969-1970, undated
    - KTEH-TV, San Jose, Calif., Founders' Society Dinner, 1993
    - “L.A. Law,” 1988-1989
    - “Lamp Unto My Feet,” 1962-1964
    - The Last Detail, 1970-1972
    - The Last Remake of Beau Geste
      - Correspondence, 1976
      - Miscellany, 1976-1977
      - Notes, 1976
      - Script, 1976
    - “Late Show with David Letterman,” 1993-1994
    - Leadbelly, 1968-1976, undated, (3 folders)
    - “Legacy: A House Divided,” 1986, n.d
    - A Lesson from Aloes
      - Broadway production
        - Contracts, 1980
        - Correspondence, 1980-1981
        - Financial records
          - 1980
          - 1981 (Box 360)
        - Miscellany, 1980-1981, undated
        - Notes, 1980-1981, undated, (3 folders)
        - Press clippings, 1980-1981
      - Yale Repertory Theatre, New Haven, Conn.
        - Correspondence, 1979-1980
        - Miscellany, 1980, undated
        - Notes, 1979-1980, undated
        - Press clippings, 1979-1980, undated
        - Script, undated
    - The Liberation of L.B. Jones, 1967-1969
    - Lincoln Museum, Fort Wayne, Ind., narration projects, 1994
    - The Lion King, 1994
    - “The Lions of Etosha: King of the Beasts,” 1984, undated
    - Live and Let Die, 1971-1972, undated
    - “Long Ago and Far Away,” 1988-1990, undated
    - “Look Up and Live,” 1962-1966
    - “Lost Tombs of Ramses,” 1989, undated
    - The Love Nest, 1962-1963
    - “Love, Sidney,” 1982
    - Macbeth, 1963-1966 (Box 361)
    - Malcolm X
      - Contracts, 1972
      - Correspondence, 1966-1977, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1970-1972, undated
      - Notes, 1966-1982, undated, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1965-1976, undated
      - Scripts, 1969-1970, undated, (4 folders)
    - The Man (Box 362)
      - Contracts, 1971-1972
      - Correspondence, 1970-1975
      - Financial records, 1971-1973
      - Miscellany, 1971-1972
      - Notes, 1970-1975, undated, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1971-1975
      - Press kit, 1972, (2 folders)
    - “Marijuana Cultivation in the U.S. National Forests Across the Country,” 1987-1988
    - Mariners' Museum, Newport News, Va., documentary, 1989, undated
    - Markebah Passion, 1980-1987, undated
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., Foundation documentary, 1974
    - Master Harold ...and the Boys
      - Broadway production
        - Correspondence, 1982-1983
        - Financial records
          - 1982
          - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 363)
        - Miscellany, 1982-1983, undated
        - Notes, 1982, undated
        - Printed matter, 1982-1983, undated
      - International tour
        - Contracts, 1983
        - Correspondence, 1982-1983, undated
        - Financial records, 1983, (6 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1982-1983, undated
        - Notes, 1982-1983, undated, (4 folders)
        - Playbills, 1983 (Box 364)
        - Press clippings, 1983
      - Miscellany, 1983-1984
    - Matewan
      - Correspondence, 1986-1991
      - Miscellany, 1986-1988
      - Notes, 1986-1987, undated
    - “Mathnet,” 1985-1994, undated
    - McDonald's Literary Achievement Awards events, 1984-1987
    - “Me and Mom”
      - Miscellany, 1984
      - Scripts
        - Production No. 1201, 1984
        - Production No. 1205, 1984
    - “The Me Nobody Knows,” 1980
    - The Medical Detectives, 1980
    - The Merchant of Venice, 1962
    - Midnight Mississippi narration, 1983-1984, undated
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1961
    - “The Mike Douglas Show,” 1974-1977
    - Milwaukee Choristers' Concert, Milwaukee, Wis., 1994
    - “The Milwaukee Family Robinson,” 1981
    - Miscellany (Box 365)
      - Agents
        - Bauman Hiller and Associates, 1985-1994
        - Camden Artists, Ltd., 1987, undated
        - Don Buchwald and Associates, 1981-1982, undated
        - J. Michael Bloom, Ltd., 1982-1984, undated
        - Jack Fields and Associates, 1981-1985, undated, (3 folders)
        - Kumin-Olenick Agency, 1963-1969, (2 folders)
        - Michael Thomas Agency, 1980-1981, undated
      - Biographical material
        - Fact sheets, 1957, 1965-1993, undated, (2 folders)
        - Press clippings, 1962-1996, undated, (3 folders) (Box 366)
      - Business trips
        - 1969, California
        - 1969-1970, Barcelona, Spain
        - 1971, California, (2 folders)
        - 1972, London, England
        - 1973-1975, California, (4 folders)
        - 1976, London, England
        - California
          - 1976, (2 folders)
          - 1977 (Box 367)
        - 1977, Washington, D.C.
        - 1978
          - California
          - London, England
        - 1980
          - California
          - Greece
        - 1981-1988, California, (5 folders)
      - Commercial prospects, 1970-1983
      - Correspondence
        - 1957-1965, (3 folders)
        - 1966-1974, (11 folders) (Box 368)
        - 1975-1978, (12 folders) (Box 369)
        - 1979-1982, (12 folders) (Box 370)
        - 1983-1986, (10 folders) (Box 371)
        - 1987
          - Jan.-May
          - June-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 372)
        - 1988-1989, (6 folders)
        - 1990, (5 folders) (Box 373)
        - 1991
          - Jan.-July, (4 folders)
          - Aug.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 374)
        - 1992, (7 folders)
        - 1993, (9 folders) (Box 375)
        - 1994
          - Jan.-Feb.
          - Mar.-Nov., (4 folders) (Box 376)
        - Undated
      - Deal memoranda, 1971-1988, undated
      - Film performances, 1989-1996
      - Honors and awards
        - Common Wealth Award, 1990-1991
        - Honorary degrees
          - 1969-1971, 1980-1984, (2 folders)
          - 1988-1994 (Box 377)
        - Miscellany, 1962-1993, (2 folders)
        - National Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, Medal for Spoken Language on the Stage, 1981
        - National Medal of Arts, 1992
      - Narration projects, 1970-1994, (2 folders)
      - Notes
        - 1957-1970, (4 folders)
        - 1971-1976, (9 folders) (Box 378)
        - 1977-1986, (8 folders) (Box 379)
        - 1987-1994, undated, (5 folders) (Box 380)
      - Organizations and committees
        - Kennedy Center Honors Artists Committee, 1979-1982
        - National Endowment for the Arts, National Council on the Arts, 1970-1984
      - Personal appearances, 1969-1984, 1990-1994
      - Personal papers
        - Family, 1970-1978, 1986, undated
        - Financial records, 1970, 1976-1977
        - Medical records, 1980-1983
        - Miscellany, 1970-1989
        - Wedding, 1982
      - Photographs, 1961, 1980, undated, (3 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1962-1994, (3 folders) (Box 381)
      - Projects under development
        - Jesse Stone television project, 1981-1982
        - Josiah Henson special, 1976
        - “Man to Man: The Earl Monroe/Bighouse Gaines Story,” 1992
        - Martin Luther King, Jr., project, 1975-1978, undated
        - Miscellany, 1969-1973, 1980-1985, 1992-1993, undated
        - One-man show, 1983-1984, 1993, undated, (2 folders)
        - Satchel Paige film, 1968-1971, undated
        - Shaka Zulu project, 1975-1987, (2 folders)
      - Public service announcements, 1970-1984, 1993-1994 (Box 382)
      - Radio work, 1961, 1970, 1980-1981, 1989
      - Representation agreements, 1961-1983, 1993, undated, (3 folders)
      - Residual payments, 1977-1985, undated
      - Schedules, 1964-1967, 1974-1994, undated, (5 folders)
      - Speaking engagements, 1973-1985, 1994
      - Stage performances, 1955-1975, undated
      - Studios and production companies (Box 383)
        - Columbia Pictures Television, 1975-1981, undated
        - Horatio Productions, 1968-1971
        - Polygram pictures, 1980-1981, undated
        - Third World Cinema, 1969-1977, undated See also Container 340, Claudine
        - Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corp., 1968-1971, undated See also Container 352, Film contracts, (2 folders)
        - Universal City Studios, 1974-1976, undated, (5 folders)
      - Submissions, 1989-1990
      - Television appearances, 1958-1960, 1969-1991, undated (Box 384)
      - Television series prospects, 1966, 1972-1989, (4 folders)
      - Treatments and script critiques, 1976-1978, 1993, undated
    - “The Missing Years of John Paul Jones,” 1984, undated
    - Mister Johnson, 1963
    - Mobile Electronics car stereos, 1994
    - Molasses to Rum to Slaves, sound recording, 1969-1970, undated
    - Moon on a Rainbow Shawl
      - Film, 1971-1976
      - Off-Broadway production, 1961-1962, undated
    - My Little Girl, 1984-1988, undated
    - My Sweet Charlie, 1966, undated
    - Nassau Community College, Garden City, N.Y., events, 1969
    - Nat Turner (Box 385)
      - Casting, 1969-1970, undated
      - Correspondence, 1968-1977, (2 folders)
      - Financial records, 1970-1971
      - Notes, 1968-1977, undated, (2 folders)
      - Press clippings, 1969-1974, 1986, undated
      - Scripts
        - Partial screenplay, undated
        - Second draft screenplay, 1969, undated, (2 folders)
        - Complete screenplay, undated, (2 folders)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration narration, 1983-1984, 1991-1992 (Box 386)
    - National Civil Rights Museum, Memphis, Tenn., narration projects, 1984, 1991
    - National Education Association commercial, 1982-1985
    - National Memorial Day Concert, Washington, D.C., 1990
    - Native Son, 1965-1966
    - “NET Playhouse”
      - “An American Christmas: Words and Music,” 1971
      - “Trumpets of the Lord,” 1968
    - New York County Democratic Committee Annual Dinner Salute to Joseph Papp, New York, N.Y., 1979
    - New York Shakespeare Festival, New York, N.Y., 1960-1991, undated
    - “New York Television Theater,” “Neighbors,” 1966
    - Newman Communications books-on-cassette, 1985, undated
    - Next Time I'll Sing to You, 1963
    - “Night of 100 Stars,” 1982-1985
    - “Night of the Hunter,” BBC Radio 4, 1992-1993
    - The Ninth Hour, 1982-1983
    - Noah II, 1982, (2 folders)
    - “Noah's Ark,” 1988-1989 (Box 387)
    - Non-Traditional Casting Symposium
      - London, England, 1989
      - Los Angeles, Calif., 1988
      - New York, N.Y., 1986-1987
    - “N.Y.P.D.” 1968-1973, undated
    - Oedipus Rex narration
      - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, Baltimore, Md., 1993, undated
      - Cleveland Orchestra, Cleveland, Ohio, 1983-1984
    - Of Mice and Men
      - Broadway production
        - Contracts, 1974-1975
        - Correspondence, 1973-1975
        - Financial records, 1974-1975
        - Miscellany, 1973-1974, undated
        - Notes, 1974-1975, undated, (3 folders)